

www.courtfolio.ca

linkedin.com/in/courtney-gibson github @CourtG courtney.giblets@gmail.com 416-346-2565 Toronto, Canada

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- Responsive design
- Website accessibility requirements
- JavaScript fundamentals
- Working with RESTful APIs, and Firebase
- React (hooks and classes)
- Version control & Git collaboration
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator
- Editing and Animation software

COURSES

Google IT Support

Indigenous Canada

UNIVERSITY OF ALBERTA

Psychological First Aid

JOHN HOPKINS UNIVERSITY

Feminism and Social Justice

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA

VOLUNTEERING

Crisis Responder

CRISIS TEXT LINE 2018 - PRESENT

Courtney Gibson

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

An adaptable and creative Front End Web Developer with a background in film production and fast-paced kitchens. I use my understanding of film and design to create an accessible experience that speaks to an inclusive audience. I am a resilient problem solver and team player with a healthy curiosity for learning new skills.

EDUCATION

2012- 2017 Immersive Web Development Bootcamp Juno College 2012- 2017 BFA Film Toronto Metropolitan University

EXPERIENCE

Sr Gelato Chef

LOLA'S GELATO MAY 2020 - APR 2022

- Created balanced gelato recipes and baked goods based on community preferences.
- Trained in all levels of the business and served as acting manager when needed.
- Responsible for digital content for social media and the website.

Nanny McPee Pet Services

NANNY MCPEE PET SERVICES MAR 2018 - APR 2019

- Co-created a dog-walking app, helping our clients know when we arrive/leave, notes, dog profiles.
- Maintained a marketing plan while engaging with the community, resulting in new clients.

Administrative Assistant

NABET 700-M UNIFOR MAR 2018 - APR 2019

- Created and organized a digital database for production files.
- Undertook research projects without supervision.
- Planned and supervised regular orientation workshops